Guide to the Scott Hubbard Papers SC1286
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-249
  - The Annual Compendium of Commercial Space Transportation, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - COECST, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - FAA Roadmapping Theme 1 Workshop, 2015 Feb 11-12 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Roadmap 2.0, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - AAM #5, 2015 Apr 27-28 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FAA AST, 2015 Feb 3-5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - RR 2.0, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ESIL - 06, 2014 May 30 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ASU talk, 2014 Oct 16-17 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - SHP EOE, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CESTAC, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - FAA AST 14, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - COE CST, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - COEST AM #3, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - COE Budgeting, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - COE Reports, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Industrial Partners, 2012-2014 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - COE CST Federal Aviation Administration Center for Excellence for Commercial Space Transportation Year 1 Annual Report Executive Summary, 2011 Dec (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - COE Tasks, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - COE TELECONS, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Married couple to Mars article, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - COE-CTS Tasks, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - COE Com TES Telecons 2012 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - COE Cost Sharing, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - COE Roadmap SU Workshop, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - COE Roadmap DC, 2011 Aug (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - COE CST, 2010 Apr 30 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - FAA COE CST LOCs, 2010 Apr (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - COE Final Matl's, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - FAA COE Endgame, 2010 Oct (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - COE Originals (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Bigelow Aerospace (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - FAA: COE - CST, 2010 Nov 10 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - COE Year 1, 2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - FAA Center of Excellence folder, 2010 Feb 9 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - EFP COE CST, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Photographs - Breakfast @ Pelicans (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - ihmc folder, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - ISU KSC VC, 2012 Jun 12 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - TPS BoD, 2012 May 7 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - TPS Board, 2011 May 29-30 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rousing, 2012 Apr (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Aero - Astro Dept. Business, 2012 Jan (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Final Shuttle, 2011 Aug (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Gate/Nest, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Sandia Gate, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sandia Gate, 2009-2012 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sandia II, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Innovation Roadshow, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - IBM Almaden, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Innovation Roadshow (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - JPL Innovation, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - F6 PDR, 2009 Feb (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - METIS - F6 Current, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Scott Hubbard travel, 2009 Oct 8-15 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - IAA, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Stanford - LMCO, 2009 Feb 24-25 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - LMCO - SU Proposal, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - CSIRO, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - OSIRIS REX, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - MAVEN, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - ORS - Accelerate, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Univ of Hawaii - Hilo, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sierra Lobo, Inc., 2009 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - SU/ARC regional climate, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Bugos-Arc History, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Augustine Panel, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - NSO - ARC/SU, 2010 Jan - May (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Fund Physics - GPB -STEP, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - SETI personnel, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Ref. plan, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Portrait, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Air bus, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Transition details, 2006 Dec (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - SETI Gig cont., 2010 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - SiV Space Bus roundtable, 2010 Aug (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - C, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - C, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - SVLG, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - The Future- electrons - NASA, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - DARPA/Kovacs, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Wired, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - CSA Board, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Space DEV, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Sub orbital - Enterprise, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Nanotech, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - CNSI, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - C, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Consulting Calbough Heinshimer (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Vanderbilt folder, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - SLVG, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - SOFIA Red Team Review, 2005 Apr 12 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - SUMG, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Zero Gravity folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Mary Ann Liebert Integrated Media Content, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ICES, 2012-2015 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ICES summary, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ICES, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ICES meeting with Bob Bishop, 2013 Nov 5-13 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - SURP, 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SURP MSR, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SURP, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - H2M TPS, 2013-2015 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - H2M TPS, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Lanetary Folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - CAPS, 2015 Apr 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The Standing Committee on Astrobiology and Planetary Science, 2013 Sep 4-6 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - CAPS, 2013 Sep 3-7 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - CAPS, 2013 Dec 17 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - CAPS, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Livermore talk, 2013 Feb 24 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - JDEM II, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - IPPW, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - SETICON II, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - ISU MBA, 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - JPC Education Panel, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Planetary Advocacy, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Planetary, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - JPL, 2014 Nov (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - The Mars Society, 2014 Aug (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Mars Soc., 2014 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Mars/Planetary, 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Mars Advocacy, 2011-2012 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Planetary Advocacy, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - 100 year starship, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Mars EDL SURP, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - JPLSample Handling coring drilling, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - SURP MSR, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - JPL/SU Collaboration (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - MAV Proposal (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - MAV NRA (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - JPL: Landing Curiosity, 2012 Aug 5 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - TPS - HOM Ongoing (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - TPS Bood DC, 2015 Apr 30 - Jun 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Planetary Society (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wash DC TPS, CSIS, 2008 Nov (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Planetary Society (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - VARC, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - SPACE X CCSAP, 2015 Jun 9-10 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Space X Adv Panel, 2014 Dec (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Space X CDR, 2014 Apr 23-24 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Space X, 2013 Nov 25 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Space X Panel, 2012 Dec 11-13 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Space X, 2013 Jul 17-19 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Space X - Adv Board (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - MSL Final Report (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - MSL Lessons Learned + Sam Dell (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - MSL-LL Interviews (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - MSL LL White Papers (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - mSL Ll Next Steps (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - OPAG, 2015 Feb 19-20 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - JPL Outer Planets, 2014 Jul 8-9 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Europa Report (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Europa (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Europa Lander Mission Concept Tecncal Review, 2012 Mar 15 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Outer Planets (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - NASA Fy 13 budget (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Scitor (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Qinetiq (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Chertoff Task (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Obama - KSC Fellow-on (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - MSL Landing, 2012 Aug 5 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - NAC Sci CMTE (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - PI Forum -4 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Museum, 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - TPS Hicc Event, 2011 Nov 3 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Jonah Z (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Tim Szwarc (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - ANES Nusc (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - AA Srydebts MT9S (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Bill Borucki (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - NSS, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Livermore Talk (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - STM/ATM w/Ames (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Space Policy NSS (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - NASA Budget (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - SIEPR (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Advocacy, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Murakami TAGA (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - NASA, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - IPPW-10 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Milan, 2010 Mar 21 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Following the Water: the New Program for Mars Exploration, 2001 Oct 1-5 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Lunar Prspector Discovery Mission (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - A Mars Enviornmental Survey Mission Concept, 1991 Jul 17-19 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary: Research and Development Recommendations for The Theoretical Understanding And Remote Sensing of Planet Biochemical Content (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Sand and Dust on Mars, 1991 Feb 4-5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Abstracts: Innovative Long Wavelength Infrared Detector Workshop (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Humans and robots: hand in grip (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Scott's Published Articles Biblio (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Lunar Prospector: Continuing Mission Results, 1999 Oct 4-8 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lunar Prospector: First results and Lessons Learned (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Original: The Lunar Prospector Gamma-ray Spectrometer (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Following the Water: the New Program for Mars Exploration, 2001 Oct 1-5 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Original: NASA's Astrobiology Institute: Initial Results of Multidisciplinary Research and Virtual Collaboration (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Lunar Prospector: First results and Lessons Learned (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - A Mars Enviornmental Survey (MESUR) - Feasibilty of a Low Cost Global Approach (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Lunar Prospoector Discovery Mission: A New Approach to Planetary Science (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Lunar Prospector: Developing a Very Low Cost Planetary Mission (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - The Lunar Prospoector Discovery Mission: A New Approach to Planetary Science (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Multi-Line Gamma-Ray Spectrometer Preformance of a Si(Li) Detector Stack, 1995 Aug (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Variable Temperature Preformance of a Si(Li) Detector Stack (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Status of Robotic Mission Studies for the Space Exploration Initiative, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - A Mars Environmental Survey (MESUR): Feasibility of a Low Cost Global Approach (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Results From A Si(Li) Gamma Ray Detector Stack for Future Mars Missions (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - MSATT Newsletter: Mars Surface and Atmosphere Through Time, 1992 Jul (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Electromagnetic Measurements of the Shielded Room at UC Davis, 1988 April (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - The Effect of Novel Deep Donors on the Resolution of Reverse Electrode Germanium Radiation Detectors, 1985 Feb (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Novel Deep Donors in As-Grown Ultrapure Germanium (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Workshop on The Martian Surface and Atmosphere Through Time (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Scientific Issues and Potential Remote-Sensing Requirements for Plant Biochemical Content (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Potassium Tantalate Niobate Thin Films for Spaceborne Pyroelectric Detectors (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Pyroelectric Detector development for the radiation measurement system (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Characterizing High-Purity Germanium Crystals for Radiation Detectors (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - MeV Gamma Ray Detection Algorithms For Stacked Silicon Detectors (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Germanium Charged Particle Telescopes with Ultra-Thin Detector Contacts (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Origin and Control of the Dominant Impurities in High-Purity Germanium (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Characterization of Polycrystalline Zone Refined Ingots of High-Purity Germanium (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Protective Surface Coating on Semiconductor Nuclear Radiation Detectors (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - The Arthur J. Dyer Observatory: A UBV Photometric Study of HS Herculis (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Zone Refining High-Purity Germanium, 1977 Oct (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Ion Implanted N-Type Contact for High-Purity Germanium Radiation Detectors (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Hydrogen-Multivalent Acceptor Complexes in High-Purity Germanium, 1977 Feb (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Divacancy-Hydrogen Complexes in Dislocation-Free High-Purity Germanium, 1976 Sep 6-9 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Bioengineering: Extending the Envelope, 1989 Sep (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - The Effect of Crystal Growth Direction on the Energy Resolution of High-Purity Germanium Detectors, 1978 Oct 18-20 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Deep Level Transient Spectroscopy of High-Purity Germanium Diodes/Detectors (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - A Two-Dimensional Position Sensitive Si(Li) Detector (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Impurity Complex Formation in Ultra-Pure Germanium, 1977 May (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Materials Aspects of Germanium Radiation Detector Fabrication (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - News Clippings (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Mars Enviormental Survey (MESUR) Pathfinder (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Proposal Volume One: FAA Center of Excellence For Commercial Space Transporatation (Box 16)
  - Proposal Volume Two: FAA Center of Excellence For Commercial Space Transporatation (Box 16)
  - Proposal for The Sentimental Mission Voume I, management, 2011 Dec 23 (Box 16)
  - Proposal for The Sentimental Mission III, Programmatics, 2011 Dec 23 (Box 16)
  - Proposal for The Sentimental Mission II, Technical, 2011 Dec 23 (Box 16)
  - Seeking A Human Spaceflight Program Worthy of a Great Nation, 2009 Oct 22 (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume II, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume V, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume V, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume VI, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume III, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume IV, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Columbia Accident Invesigation Board Report Volume V, 2003 Oct (Box 16)
  - Name Tags (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lunar Prospector Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Bookmarks (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - STS-107 Medals, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 21st Space Operations Squadron Medal (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bigelow Aerospace Ephemera/Memorabilia (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - NYLF Keychain (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Photos + Programs (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Boeing Pins (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Clippings - Mars (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Mars Pathfinder - Photos + Promotional Material (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Clippings - Mars (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Clippings + Photos, Mars (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Mars Pathfinder Landing, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - MESUR (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - MESUR Brochures + Pins (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Planetfest, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Pictures -LP -Pa Thefindes (Box 18)
  - Mars Exploration Payload Analysis Group (MEPAG) Meeting Notes and Viewgraphs, 2001 Apr 16-18 (Box 18)
  - International Mars Exploration Working Group (IMEWG) Meeting Viewgraphs, 2001 Jun 8 (Box 18)
  - Phoenix A/EDL Critical Events Readiness Review, 2008 Apr 17 (Box 18)
  - Phoenix Surface Critical Event Readiness Review, 2008 Apr 18 (Box 18)
  - Proceedings of the Mars Global Network Mission Workshop, 1990 Feb 6-7 (Box 18)
  - 37th Lunar and Planetary Science Confence Program to Technical Session (Box 18)
  - NAI, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Speaking Requests, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Speaking Engagements, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tranparencies (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - NASA Ames Visitor Center (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Strategic Research Center (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ames Ware 5 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - R.A. Grymes Ph.D Letter, 2007 Feb 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Rank Awards Scott Hubbard, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Photos / Hubbard G.S Photos, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Astrobiology Roadmap (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - U. Kentuckey (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Faculty Fol Workshop (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - CCST (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - CCST (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous / Set 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Rabothes (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Sally Ride (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Sabdua Nat'l Labs (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Basic 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Basic: Bay Area Science Infrastructure Consortium (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Carl Sagan Center (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Kepler: A Search For Terrestial Planets (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Manoteua (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Ihmc (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Instrumentation Study (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ARC/JSC Mov, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - JSC/ARC Mov Background (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Amos Astrogram (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Transparencies (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ames Vision Revisited (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Kepler (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Kepler Manager (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Kepler (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kepler Evals + Dorumnselect (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Kepler Red Team @ Ball, 2001 Jul 1-3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Kepler Budget / Replan, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Kepler (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Maus Airplane MAT (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - MARS Airplane NRL (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - MARS Airplane (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - MARS Airplane (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Mars Airplane Redux, 1999 July (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Mars Airplane Maum/Coder/HQ, 1999 Apr 14 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Mars Airplane Current/imd NPL Visits (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Okeefe, 1006 Jun (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Okeyle Brief, 2004 Jun 7 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Virgin Galactic (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Av Week Viewpoint (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Av Week - 50 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Stanford GSB (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Empathy Nonrvav Space (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Astrogram (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Scott's IPA to Seti (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Transforming, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - ULA (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Regional Climate (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Regional Climate Change (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Scott Hubbard (Dick Johnson) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Synthetic Life (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Ab ScvCon (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - NAC - Subcamte (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - UCSD (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - My Business Future Directions (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - LMMS, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - KACST (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - ERT Corp (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - TPS (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Predictive Space Markets (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Accidents (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - JPL Visits (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Flora - Aero Capture to Thermal (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - NAMS Gold Team (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - NAMS - Red Team (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - NAMS - 2014 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Wyer, 2012-2013 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - APL, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - APL (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - SPUTnik Movie And Op-ED - Chronids (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - SPUTNIk Hoffman (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Schwob (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Ed Hoffman Letter (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - CSA, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - SETI-Bot (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - AB, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - SVLG (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - HRH BEP (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - HQs - Mars (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Talks (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - NASA Alumni League (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - SOFIA, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - HSTC, 2009 Aug 18 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Surrey (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Pardee/GSA Colloq, 2010 Nov 2 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - JPL, 2014 Mar 12-13 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - JPL Consulting (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - JPL, 2008 Aug 18-19 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - JPL Mi + Culture Study (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - LASP Review (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - LASP, 2008 Jan 23 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Stetson Discovery / N.F Review (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - JPL Consult, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Firouz (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - JPL Cons, etc (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - UCB-SSL (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - CAL-OSTP (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Sloan (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Pioneer Prods (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - CABROL (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - TPS (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Bob Bishop (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - UCSC (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Challenger (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Cogswell (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Lumeneon Society (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Burkhart AASTA (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Sir Maden Udem (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - TNO (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Memorable (Box 22)
  - Scott Hubbard Oracle Calen, 2006 Mar - 2012 Dec (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - SSE @ 50 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - MSL Launch, 2011 Nov 25 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Mars Habitability Lisbon, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - JMART (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - JMART, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - JMAER, 2011 Oct 5-6 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - MARS S.R.B, 2016 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - MSL Review (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - IMARS Paris, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Mars, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mars, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Phoenix Risk Review (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - FY09 Budget NASA-SSE (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Mars Review, 2016-2018 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Mart iMart (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Mart II, 2009 Jun 8-10 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - MART, 2009 Apr 16-17 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - MEPAGs (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Rome, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Scott Hubbard: Travel Roma, Italy, International Science Festival (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - B612-Sentinel LA, 2015 Jul 10-11 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Astroid Capture (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sentinel Planning, 2015 Mar 25-26 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sentinel NXT (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sentinel Moore (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sentinel Talks (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Queen, 2014 Jul 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - B612 Donors Telecons (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - McAdoo (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - PHIL Yoong, 2013 Oct 22 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - B612, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - DC, May 7-9 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - BALL/Sentinel, 2013 Mar 10-21 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Meteor Crager B612 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - B612 Post Rollout (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - B612 - DC/OSTP Visit (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - B612 Review, 2012 Sep 11-13 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - B612 - Neo (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - B612, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - B612 Rollout (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Pictures (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Lessons Learned in Decadal Planning in Space Science: A Workshop, 2012 Nov 12-13 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The Steering Group for the SSB Planetary Decadal Survey, 2012 Feb 22-24 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Decadal Survey, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Decadal Town Hall (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Decadal Tasks (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - AIAA Fellows Dinner Arlington, VA, 2010 May 10-12 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - NRC Panel SSEXP Review (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - The Steering Group for the Committee on Planetary Science Decadal Survey, 2009 Jul 6-8 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - NRC Decadal (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - The Steering Group for the SSD Planetary Decadal Survey, 2010 Jul 13-15 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - The Steering Group for the SSD Planetary Decadal Survey, 2010 Aug 3-4 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Si(Li) Stack Vugraphs (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Diaz Viewgraphs, 1995 Aug 15 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Jeff Cuzzi (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Dick Pehl (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: EE Haller (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - SF Notes, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - S Notes, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Science Unseietics, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - NRP, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Inaugural Planning (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - SPL/ARC Strat Alliance, 2001 Oct 9 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - JPL ARC Tech Transition (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Proj MGL Quddiration (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - MSR / EEV, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - MECA John Marshall (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - From Billboard (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - NASA-ARC Signuo (Box 27, Folder 17)